

Hugh Caluscusin

Full-stack JavaScript Developer

Info

Zone 6, Bascon St., Graceville Homes, Brgy Dumlog, Talisay Cebu, 6045, Philippines

∂ Phone

+639559328520

Email

hughcaluscusin@gmail.com

⊗ Portfolio

www.hughcaluscusin.com

Skills

Languages

JavaScript (ES6+), PHP7+, GraphQL, CSS3/Sass, HTML5

≈ Frameworks

React, NextJS, CRA, Node/ Express, WordPress, WorkBox, Apollo, GraphQL-Yoga, Prisma, Redux

⊘ Tools

Git/GitHub, Webpack, CLI, Ngrok, Postman, ESLint/Prettier, LogRocket

○ Platforms

Heroku, AWS EC2, Zeit/Now, Netlify, cPanel/Apache

Design & Other

Photoshop, Adobe XD, Jest Wireframing, Enzyme, MySQL MongoDB, PostgreSQL, Firebase, Travis, CI

Profile

Dedicated freelance programmer, shifted from being a PHP developer to become a fullstack JavaScript developer. More than 3 years of PHP experience and about 2 years of fullstack JavaScript experience. Skilled in ES6+ and Node and React (NextJS), eager to join your team to provide both frontend and backend solutions to your clients. Able to work in a team or as solo. In freelance world, proper handling of clients and delivering their products on time are the main keys, gradually learned those through the years.

Employment History

Web/App Developer, Freelancing

Jan 2015 - Present

© Cebu, Philippines

Build simple to custom web applications with conventional workflows and technologies.

Web Developer, Rose Institute

Dec 2012 - Dec 2013

O Cebu, Philippines

Designed and developed their business website from the ground up.

Education

University of South Wales, MSc, Computing & Electronics Technology

Sep 2016 - Jan 2018 💮 Llantwit Road, Treforest, UK

Informatics Computer Institute, BS, Information Technology

Jan 2009 - Apr 2012 © Cebu, Philippines

Systems Technology Institute, AD, Computer & Electronics Technology

Jun 2004 - Mar 2006 © Dumaguete, Philippines

References

References available upon request.

Interests

Songwriting, Music Production, Table Tennis, Frisbee, Outdoors, Learning new stuff